Anastasia Gladun

Full Stack Web Developer

PERSONAL DETAILS

Mobile: 021 03 03387

Email: anastasiagladoun@gmail.com

Website: https://anastasia-gladun.netlify.app

SUMMARY

I have always been passionate about technology and even started my carrier as an IT manager. However, I wanted to be more involved in the technical part of the process and after a few years of being in and out of the IT world, I decided to chase my passion.

I have recently graduated from Enspiral Dev Academy, where I practiced agile methodologies and had experience in dev tools while developing a range of software applications and working in diverse teams. For the final project, my team and I created a complete web app from scratch, both the back end and the front end using HTML5, CSS3, React, Redux and MySQL. I had an opportunity to demonstrate an ability to learn fast and work with strict deadlines and apply my skills while learning new tools and technologies and communicating with the team.

KEY SKILLS

Technical skills

- JavaScript, ECMAScript 6.
- React.js, Redux, JSX.
- Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars.js (server-side rendering and APIs).
- MySQL, Knex.js, PostgreSQL.
- Unit testing: Supertest, Cheerio, Jest.
- HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Skeleton, Bootstrap.
- GitHub, Command line.
- Pair-programming.
- Agile practices.

Soft skills

- Customer service experience.
- Problem-solving.
- Multi-tasking.
- Ability to work in a team and individually.
- Planning and organizational skills.
- Self-management, time-management.

EXPERIENCE

Enspiral Dev Academy

March 2021 - August 2021, Wellington

Full-stack JavaScript boot camp focused on ES5/6, Node.js, React, Redux.

Web development program projects:

- Seasons
- Personal Blog
- Scale

Tech for Good - An app for recreational fishers to record their catch, get weather data, and ultimately build a dataset to monitor and maintain levels of fish species.

Wellington Sourdough

June 2019 - April 2021, Wellington Pastry chef

Croc Incorporated

January 2011 -December 2015, Moscow

Moscow System Integrator / Service Delivery Manager

Responsibilities

- Customer service and support in Computer and Storage System Department.
- Coordinating service calls for warranty support/Responsible for meeting SLA requirements.
- Cooperation with leading IT hardware vendors: Dell, HP, IBM, EMC, Oracle, Hitachi, Symantec.
- Coordinating the work process between several departments and work teams.
- Part's logistics management, using vendors' control systems.
- Presentations for new colleagues.

EDUCATION

• Enspiral Dev Academy, 2021 Wellington

Qualification: Enspiral Dev Academy Web Development Training Scheme

• Udemy, 2021 Online

Qualification: The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery

The National University of Science and Technology, 2011 Moscow
Qualification: Applied computer science